copper?
どう?
Are you two filming together?
2人で撮ってる?
I didn't take any pictures.
全然撮ってない
Hey, this camera internet is too small.
ちょっとね、このカメラインターネット小さすぎて、
I didn't take a picture though.
撮らなかったんだけど
Because I'm taking pictures today.
今日は撮ってるからな、と
Yay.
イエーイ
This kid is really cute, really.
ほんとこの子可愛いね、めっちゃ
It's so cute.
めちゃめちゃ可愛い
This belt is also cute.
このベルトも可愛い
Right?
でしょ?
Okay, does it suit you?
いいじゃん、似合ってる?
thank you.
ありがとう
There are a lot of people.
人多いね
Hey, there are a lot of cars.
ねえ、車も多い
There are a lot of cars, that's for sure.
車多いね、確かに
It's a holiday, so everyone is going out.
休みだから、みんなお出かけなんだ
Because it's Saturday and Sunday.
土日だからね
So are we.
俺らもそうだけどね
I'm walking.
歩いてる
It's eco, eco.
エコだよ、エコ
Look at the camera.
カメラ見てみて
Ah, that's cute.
あ、可愛いね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm happy to meet you after a long time.
久々に会えて嬉しいよ
Hey, summer too.
ねえ、夏も
Hey, come on, where are you going?
ねえ、さあ、どこ行ってとかある?
You know, I want to go to the cat cafe I saw the other day.
あのね、この前見てた猫カフェ行きたい
Sorry to keep you waiting.
ごめん、お待たせ
long time no see.
久しぶり
Not at all, I just arrived.
全然、今来たとこ
Why are you taking pictures?
なんで撮ってるの?
this?
これ?
be on one's mind.
気になる
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
We haven't seen each other in a long time, so it's a great date,
今日は久々に会うから、せっかくのデートだし、
I thought I'd like to go on a date with the camera rolling.
カメラ回しながらデートしたいなと思って
picture?
え?
No way.
やだ
Why do you say no?
なんでやだとか言う?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Close, close.
近い近い
I'll take a lot of shots.
撮影量をとるよ
Do you go through the office?
事務所通す?
Go through the office.
事務所通って
May I?
いいですか?
Go through the office.
事務所通って
Is it no good?
ダメですか?
Because I'm not in a good mood.
ノリいないからね
But I think it's a little embarrassing,
でもさ、ちょっと恥ずかしいと思うけど、
I'm embarrassed too.
俺も恥ずかしいから
It's a commemoration.
記念じゃん
Because I was able to meet you.
せっかく会えたんだからさ
Mine is embarrassing.
私のが恥ずかしい
It's a memory, so let's go on a date while taking pictures of it.
思い出だからさ、これカメラ撮りながらデートしようよ
No way.
やだ
No?
やだ?
No way.
やだ
やだって
I want to spin it, so I'll spin it.
俺回したいから回すから
For now, I haven't decided where to go yet.
とりあえずまだどこにか決まってないからさ、
Shall we just walk for a while?
ちょっととりあえず歩こうか
Got it.
分かった
Oh, it's happening.
え、なってるな
I like your outfit today.
今今日服装いいね
real?
ほんと?
Are you going to take it all the time?
ずっと取るの?
that.
それ
terrible.
やばい
Do you want to be seen together?
2人で映りたい?
If I were to make it, two people would go.
作るなら2人が行っちゃう
just me?
私だけ?
cute.
かわいい
Please say that.
そんなこと言ってくれ
Be careful of the camera though.
カメラ警戒かけど
copper?
どう?
Do you want to take pictures with two people?
2人で撮る?
I never took pictures.
絶対撮ってない
Hey, this camera-in-camera is too small.
ちょっとね、このカメラインカメラ小さすぎて、
I didn't take a picture though.
撮らなかったんだけど
Because you can see my hands.
手が映ってるからな
This kid is really cute, really.
ほんとこの子かわいいね、めっちゃ
It's so cute.
めちゃめちゃかわいい
Real dates are cute too.
本当デートもかわいい
Right?
でしょ?
It's okay, it suits you.
いいじゃん、似合ってる
That's wonderful.
素敵だね
thank you.
ありがとう
There are quite a lot of people there.
結構人多いね
Hey, there are a lot of cars.
ねえ、車も多い
There are a lot of cars, that's for sure.
車多いね、確かに
It's a holiday, so everyone is going out.
休みだから、みんなお出かけなんだな
Because it's Saturday and Sunday.
土日だからね
So are we.
俺らもそうだけどね
I'm walking.
歩いてるもん
It's eco, eco.
エコだよ、エコ
Look at the camera.
カメラ見てみて
Ah, that's cute.
あ、かわいいね
Ah, that's embarrassing.
あ、恥ずかしい
I'm happy to meet you after a long time.
久々に会えて嬉しいよ
Hey, over there.
ねえ、あそこ
Where are you going?
どこ行ってとかある?
I want to go to the cat cafe I saw the other day.
この前見てた猫カフェ行きたい
Cat cafe?
猫カフェ?
That sweet dish?
あの甘みせん?
oh yeah.
そうそう
I saw your photo the last time we met.
前会った時に写真見したじゃん
I've always wanted to go there,
あそこずっと行きたいって思ったから、
Let's go today.
今日行こうよ
Cat: Actually, I've never been to a cafe.
猫 カフェ行ったことなくてさ、実は
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
I'm wasting my life.
人生損してる
Shall we go then?
じゃあ行くか
Are you healed?
癒される?
Will the cat come?
猫ちゃんやってくるかな?
If you have a snack.
おやつ持てば
Shall we go to a cat cafe then?
じゃあ猫カフェ行くか
Let's go, let's go.
行こう、行こう
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
行 こう、 行こう、行こう
Arrived at the cat cafe.
猫カフェに到着
There are so many cats.
めっちゃ、いる猫いるね
cute.
可愛い
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
Do you want to touch this?
これ触る?
Are you on vacation?
お休み中かな?
Really.
めっちゃ
Are you on vacation?
お休み中?
I'm used to it.
慣れなんです
Is this some sort of cat document?
これ、猫の書類的なのかな?
Ah, it's here.
あ、来た
It came, it came, it came.
来た、来た、来た
The cat is here, the cat is here, the cat is here
猫ちゃん来た、猫ちゃん来た、猫ちゃん来た、
The cat came.
猫ちゃん来た
why?
なんで?
I know a lot of things.
いろいろ言い知るんだけど
picture?
え?
Just to get your cat's attention,
ちょっとさ、 猫ちゃんのさ、 気を引くためにさ、
Actually, I brought something nice.
俺、いいもの持ってきたんだ、実は
Something good?
いいもの?
yes.
はい
Cat play.
猫じゃらし
It's funny.
じゃらしね
Well then, let's play with this cat.
じゃあ、この猫ちゃん遊ぼう
Maybe he'll take care of me.
かまってくれるかも
Pay attention.
かまって
Pay attention, pay attention.
かまって、かまって
Pay attention.
かまって
This child, this child, this child.
この子、この子、この子
This kid can go, right?
この子、行けるんじゃない?
Can you go?
行ける?
Ah, I'm gone.
あ、行っちゃった
It's there too.
そこにもいる
Wait, maybe you're on vacation due to the time?
ちょっと、時間帯的に お休み中なのかな?
hey.
ね
Yeah.
うん
I'm tired of being too human.
人間構えすぎて疲れた
I'll play around with it for a while and take some pictures.
ちょっと、遊んでとこ撮っちゃう
Huh?
あれ?
You're working on it now.
今、手づくろいしていらっしゃる
The cat.
お猫様が
He is preparing his hands.
手づくろいしていらっしゃる
Cat has just eaten food.
猫ちゃん、ご飯食べたばっかでね
Maybe he's on vacation.
お休み中なのかもしれないね
But cats sleep 80% of the day.
でも猫はね、 1日の8割は寝てるんだよ
Quick trivia.
急に雑学
Okay, okay, ah, we're still talking.
よし、よし、あ、今でも 話してる、
I'm talking.
話してる
Is that correct?
それ、合ってる?
How to use it.
使い方
It definitely doesn't match.
絶対、合ってないよね
Indifferent.
無関心
terrible.
やばい
It's better for us to give up.
もう諦めたほうがいい、俺ら
I can't help but be interested.
全然関心しむしかない
He might have hated it.
嫌われたかもしれない
I hate it, same thing.
嫌いですね、同じ
It's really fluffy though.
すっごいモフモフなんだけど
Seriously?
マジ?
I hated it a little.
ちょっと嫌がった
You hated me.
嫌われちゃったね
Seriously?
マジ?
Sleep, something.
寝て、何か
Magura?
マグラ?
surely.
確かに
It's a natural muffler.
天然のマフラーだね
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
It's so bushy.
ふさふさだね
All the cats here are fluffy.
ここの猫、みんなふさふさやな
There are a lot of super strong moves.
超猛手が多い
But that's it.
でも、あれだね
I just didn't have much interest in cats.
あまり猫に関心をもたえなかったということで
With sadness.
悲しい思いで
I felt sad.
悲しい思いでなりました
Cat, you're on vacation, so would you like to move?
猫ちゃん、お休み中だから 移動しますか
Do you want to move?
移動するか
Let's move a little.
ちょっと移動しよう
arrival.
到着
When we arrived, we found ourselves at a hotel.
到 着ってホテルなんですけど
It's a hotel.
ホテルですね
It's a hotel though.
ホテルですけど
Well, he's taking pictures again.
てか、また撮ってるじゃん
Ah, this.
あ、これね
Of course it's a hotel.
ホテルっていうのもまずね
There were a lot of people, to be honest.
人混みがさ、 多かったじゃん、正直
Well, certainly.
まあ、確かに
It was Saturday and Sunday, so there were a lot of people.
土日でさ、人多くてさ
There were also many cat cafes.
猫カフェも多かったでしょ
There were many.
多かった
There were more people.
人がもう、人の方が多かった
From the cat.
猫ちゃんより
So I thought I'd like to take it easy and talk indoors.
だからゆっくりさ、 室内で話したいなと思ってさ、
For two people.
2人で
Do I need to turn the camera?
カメラ回す必要ある?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Also, the date isn't over yet.
あと、まだデート終わってないじゃん
We're still on a date.
まだデート中だよ
Yes, but.
そうだけど
Today, I decided to take a photo of our date with my camera, to keep it as a memory.
今日思い出にさ、残すためにさ、 カメラでデート撮ろうって言
Because it happened.
った から
Even here?
ここでも?
Here too.
ここでも
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
A field trip is a field trip until you return home.
遠足は帰るまでが遠足だよ
A date is still a date until you get home.
デートも帰るまでがデートだよ
So let's go home and take pictures on the way home?
じゃあ 帰りもう、帰りもう撮るってこと?
I go home while taking pictures.
撮りながら帰る
Does it have charging?
充電持つ?
Well, come on, I'll use it for a while.
じゃあさ、ちょっとさ、 つかくだからさ、
Do you want to chat?
おしゃべりする?
Or do you do something like this?
それともこういうことする?
Hey, no.
ねえ、ダメ
Oh, no?
あ、ダメ?
sorry.
ごめん
How have you been lately?
最近どうなの?
For example, school.
例えば、学校とかね
School has been calming down lately.
学校はね、 最近落ち着いてきてるよ
It's starting to calm down.
落ち着いてきてるんだ
You said you were kind of busy.
なんか忙しいって言ってたけど
Yes, I was busy getting my teaching license.
そう、教員免許取るのに 忙しかったから
I was just studying.
勉強してたんだけどね
Yes, I passed the exam the other day.
そう、この前なんと 合格したんです
Seriously?
マジで?
Did you take it?
取ったの?
Teacher's license.
教員免許
Yes, I got it.
そう、取れた
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
I did my best.
頑張ったんだよ
You did your best.
頑張ったね
What is the subject?
科目なんなの?
The subject is Japanese.
科目はね、国語
It's the Japanese language.
国語なんだ
Yarn sweets.
糸お菓子
He seems to have a head.
頭あるそう
surely.
確かに
It's Rashaumon, right?
ラショーモンでしょ
Like Rashaumon.
ラショーモンとかね
Teach me.
教えるんだ
Teacher's licenses are for high school, junior high school, etc.
教員免許はね、 高校とか中学とか
I'm a high school student.
私はね、高校の方
Looks difficult.
難しそう
Since we are so close in age, it's hard to tell which one is the student.
歳が近いから、 どっちが学生か分かんなくなっちゃう
surely.
確かに
I don't really understand this, but...
これってさ、俺あんまよく 分かってないんだけどさ、
I got my teaching license and it was like job hunting.
教員免許取ってさ、 就活みたいな感じでさ、
There's job hunting all around.
周り就活じゃん
It's like job hunting, and there's an interview at school.
なんか就活みたいな感じでさ、 学校になんかその 面談みたいな
Is there an interview?
さ、 面接とかある?
Yes, I will.
うん、するする
Educational training, etc.
教育実習とかね
Is that so?
そういうことか
1 month.
1ヶ月
How much did you do?
ど れくらいやったかな?
I went to the school, saw the atmosphere, and thought,
学 校に行って、 雰囲気見て、 ふんふん、
I see.
なるほどって
I'm going to study.
勉強しに行くの
That's right.
そうなんだ
It's okay to be a teacher trainee, don't you get called out to?
教育実習生って結構さ、 声かけられたりしない?
Oh, well, I was really popular.
あーもうね、すごいモテた
That's hilarious.
うわきじゃん
I'm not crazy.
うわきじゃないよ
Girl, you had a great conversation.
女の子ね、すごい話かけられたよ
Teacher, do you have a boyfriend?
先生、彼氏いるの?
Did I say I'm fine?
ちゃんといるって言った?
real?
ほんと?
You said it.
言 ったよね
Said.
言いました
It's amazing, look at the pictures, look at the pictures.
すごいね、写真見して写真見して
Did you see it?
見したの?
I haven't seen it.
見してないよ
If I touch my phone, I'll get angry.
携帯触ってたら怒られちゃうから
Sorry, sorry, that's right, that's right.
ご めんごめん、そっかそっかそっか
Because I don't have a smartphone.
スマホ持ってないから
It was so cute.
可愛かったなぁ
That's nice, it's sparkling.
いい ね、キラキラしてるよね
Yes, it was dazzling.
そう、眩しかった
But from now on, I will teach such children.
でも今後そういう子たち教えるんだよ
You'll feel young again.
もう一回青春してくるね
When I'm not being strict, if I see a student talking,
厳しくいかない時には、 喋ってる生徒いたら、
Throw chalk, properly.
チョーク投げるんだよ、ちゃんと
There!
そこ!
Let's practice now, chalk throwing.
今練習しよう、チョーク投げる
Do you want to practice?
練習する?
I can't talk there.
そこ喋れない
What should I do if they snap my lips?
どうしよう、口パチンって取られたら
I'll do it, you'll do it.
やるなぁ、お前やるなぁ
What kind of school?
どういう学校?
By the way, getting a teaching license is...
ちなみに、教員免許を取るのって、
The level is the same for each university.
大学ごとにレベル一定なの
Are the levels different for each faculty of education?
その教育学部ごとに、 レベルって違うの?
Is it different?
違うのかな?
Where is school now?
今、学校どこだっけ?
I'm now back at Chuo University.
今、中央大学に帰っているよ
Yes, Chuo University.
そうだ、中央大学
Did you forget?
忘れてたの?
I haven't forgotten.
忘れてないよ
I forgot, you're smart.
忘れてたの、頭いいんだよ、とか
surely.
確かに
It's okay to finally do it though.
やっともいいけどね
Because it's a bit stupid.
ちょっとバカだから
You forgot, most of the time.
忘れてたでしょ、大抵
I'm sorry.
申し訳ございません
I would like to apologize.
謝罪させていただきます
No alcohol.
お酒ございません
That's fine.
いいでしょう
As a Japanese language teacher, I would like to apologize for my use of language.
俺でも国語の先生的に言葉使いの 謝罪させていただきます
20 circles.
20丸
20 circles, I'll give you Hanamaru.
20丸、花丸あげる
It's sweet.
甘いなぁ
That's sweet, me.
甘いなぁ、私
Be more sweet.
もっと甘やかして
Then, I'll get my teaching license and then I'll be assigned.
じゃあ、教員免許を取って、 あとはその配属、
Deciding on a school is like a match.
学校決まるの マッチみたいな感じなんだもんね
I agree.
そうだね
I feel like I have freed up some time for my private life.
時間のプライベート的に 空きもできたって感じだよね
Until spring.
春まではね
That's fine.
いいじゃん
It's a hobby, I'm sorry to call it a hobby, but
趣味でさ、 趣味って言ったら悪いけど、
As a music cruise.
音楽クルスとしてじゃん
Oh, that girl band?
ああ、あのガールズバンド?
Are you still working on it?
まだ組んでるの?
Not yet, I'm working on it.
まだね、組んでるよ
But how much?
でも、どれくらいだろう?
It's been about 3 or 4 months since everyone has been so busy that we haven't been able to get together.
3、4ヶ月くらいもね、 みんな忙しく集まれてないんだ
Is it Relta's front line?
レルタ最前線だっけ?
Why do you remember my name?
なんで名前覚えてるの?
Even though I forgot the name of the school.
学校名忘れてるくせに
No, I thought the name was sparkling.
いや、キラキラだなと思って名前
Certainly.
確かにね
I thought it was a great name.
すごい名前だなーって 思いながら
Good sense.
センスいいや
Well then, I guess I got through it during a busy period.
じゃあ、せっかくさ、 忙しい時期に乗り越えたわけじゃん
I think I will continue to be busy,
これからもね、忙しいと思うけど、
It's not like I can take a little break.
ちょっとさ、休みできるわけじゃん
I agree.
そうだね
What do you want to do on your day off right now?
今、休みの日とかさ、 何したいとかある?
I want to go on a date.
デートしたい
With bare hands like this, you look like a man.
こんな素手、 さらっと、めっちゃ男目みたいになったね
After all, it's been a long time, even today.
だって、久しぶりじゃん、今日だって
surely.
確かに
I was so happy to meet you today.
今日会えたの、すごい嬉しかった
About a month.
1ヶ月ぐらいか
It's been a while.
久しぶりだね
Do you want to go on a date?
デートしたいの?
I want to go on a date.
デートしたい
Don't do it.
つかやらないで
I'll do it soon.
つかやっちゃう
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
Still on camera.
まだカメラで
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
I don't know where to look.
どっちに目を合わしたらいいか分からない
Me, keep an eye on me.
俺、見といて
But, it's been a while since we last had that date.
でもね、久しぶりそのデートでさ、
It was my first time at a cat cafe too, and I had a lot of fun.
俺も初めての猫カフェで、 結構楽しかったんだけど、
I guess I took a little break today.
なんか、 今日なんかでもちょっとお休みしてたね、
Cat.
猫ちゃん
Hey, everyone was watching with full stomachs.
ねえ、みんなお腹いっぱいで見てた
You saw it.
見てたね
What is a cat cafe like?
猫カフェってあんな感じなの?
Yeah, it's like that.
うん、あんな感じ
Ah, that's what it feels like.
あ、あんな感じなんだ
They won't come near you unless you have a snack.
おやつ持ってないと近寄ってくれないから
It would be a good idea to bring snacks.
おやつ持っときゃよかったね
Hey.
ねえ
Gacha Gacha.
ガ チャガチャして
Sure, I made a mistake.
確かに、ミスったわ
Next time, let's do it.
次ちょっとさ、やろうよ
Yeah, I want to do it.
うん、やりたい
I want to go again.
また行きたい
But you know, I thought I'd play with the cat,
でも ね、猫ちゃんと戯れると思ってたから、
Do you feel lonely?
なんか、 寂しいというか、 寂 しい?
There's a cat in front of me.
目の前に猫ちゃんいるからさ
Hey, don't say anything weird.
ねえ、 変なこと言わないでよ
Give me a little nyan meow.
ちょっとにゃんにゃんしてよ
Serve me, please meow.
サービスしてよ、にゃんにゃんしてよ
Meow, meow, here you go.
にゃんって、にゃんって、ほら
Meow, meow.
にゃんって、にゃーんって
Use both hands and say "meow" more.
もっと、両手でさ、 にゃーんってして
Meow.
にゃーん
Nyan.
に ゃ ーん
I don't like it!
嫌だ!
I love you, meow.
好きだ、にゃーんって
好きだ、にゃーん
Well then, a little more, a little more.
じゃあさ、 ちょっとさ、もっとさ、
It's like a cat, it's like a cat pose,
猫っぽくさ、 猫のポーズみたいになってさ、
Please say meow.
にゃーんってしてよ
Cat pose?
猫のポーズ?
Four inches?
四寸倍?
It's like four inches bigger.
四寸倍みたいな
Are you going?
行か?
Ah, okay.
あ、いいよ
Well, sit down.
その、座っておいて
Let's go.
行 くわ
Let's go, I said "Nyaan".
行 くよ、にゃーんってして
Nyan.
に ゃ ーん
When it's sweet, I say meow.
甘いと甘いと、にゃーんって
Meow.
にゃーん
It's cute, okay?
かわいいよ、よっちゃ
Don't lean on me!
よらないで!
Please don't come, meow.
よらないでほしい、にゃんって
lie?
嘘?
I don't think the camera is very good, though.
カメラはよとだめだと思うけどさ、
Shouldn't I get too close?
俺も近づいちゃだめ?
I'm fine.
俺はいいよ
Oh, is that okay?
あ、いいの?
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ、嫌だ
lie?
嘘?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘だろ?
Can I come closer?
近づいていい?
Which one do you want me to approach?
それから近づいてほしい、どっち?
Okay.
いいよ
That's good.
いい方だ
Well, come on, now that we're two,
じゃあ ちょっとさ、 二人になったからさ、
Let's get a little closer.
ちょっとだけ近づこうよ
Yeah.
うん
I'll go behind you.
後ろ行くからさ
Close to camera.
カメラ近
Well then, try it again. Meow meow.
じゃあもう一回やってよ、 にゃんにゃんってして
Meow meow.
にゃんにゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
picture?
え?
sexual harassment!
セクハラ!
It's not sexual harassment, is it?
セクハラじゃないでしょ
Is there anything wrong with that?
別にだめなの?
No!
だめ!
No.
違うよ
It's cute.
可愛いね
Have you noticed?
気づいてるかな?
Did something hit me on the back?
俺さ、背中になんか当たってない?
Honestly, a little.
正直ちょっと
Hey.
ねぇ
Doesn't it hit your back a bit?
背中にちょっと当たってない?
That's right.
当たってる
What was it?
何が当たってたの?
I won't say it.
言わない
It's meow meow.
にゃんにゃんださ
I can't stand it any longer.
もうちょっと我慢できない
It's a little early though.
もうちょっと早いけどさ
At the hotel.
ホテルでさ
Let's meow meow.
にゃんにゃんしよう
Let's have a good time.
に ゃ んにゃんしよう
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you going to take pictures?
撮るの?
this.
これ
I want to take a picture.
撮りたい
No.
だめだよ
No?
だめなの?
Isn't it the best memory?
最高の思い出じゃない?
Take a picture, the two of us together.
撮ってさ、2人で一緒に
I don't like it!
嫌だ!
Because that's right.
そうやから
It's a shoe play.
シューチプレイじゃん
I'm a man after all, so there are times like that.
俺もさ、やっぱ 男だから、そういう時も あるわけ
I felt lonely.
寂しくなった
I'll definitely post it somewhere.
絶対 どっかに載せるじゃん
I can't post it.
載 せないよ
You'll show it to someone.
誰かに見せるでしょ
I don't want to show it.
見せたくないもんね
There's no such person, right?
そんな奴いないでしょ
Although there may be.
いるかもしれないけど
Because I don't.
俺はしないからさ
Believe me.
信じて
Can I ride?
乗っけていい?
No.
ダメ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Can I ride?
乗っけていい?
Say something like that.
とか言って
It's good to ride.
乗っけていいね
Since I can't ride it, I'll make sure that it's just me and see it at a glance.
乗っけないから、本当に 俺だけの一目で見るようにするから
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Just a little.
ちょっとだけだよ
Just a little bit okay?
ちょっとだけいい?
Eh, here it is.
えー、こら
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Is it okay just for a little while?
ちょっと だけ いい の?
Just a little.
ちょっとだけだよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Let me know if it doesn't work.
ダメってなったら 言ってね
See you then.
じゃあさ
I'll say it.
言うね
a little bit.
ちょっと
A newly dating couple.
付き合いたてのカップル
There's an exciting scene going on.
ウイウイシーンがなっているんだ
Your face is bright red.
顔真っ赤じゃん
My face is so red.
めちゃめちゃ顔真っ赤じゃん
Your face is red, are you okay?
顔赤いよ、大丈夫?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
embarrassed
恥ずか
Yes.
しい
I took lots of pictures with my camera.
カ メラでいっぱい撮ってたよ
Say yay, yay.
イエーイ、イエーイとか言って
Did it get bigger again?
また大きくなった?
Yeah.
ええ
Don't say things like that.
そういうこと言わないで
How many cups did you get?
何カップになったの?
Things like school.
学校とかやさ
High exposure.
露出の高いさ
beautiful.
綺麗
I don't like it.
好 きないよ
There are also a lot of male high school students.
専屋高生なオスドもいっぱいあるからさ
You won't be attacked.
襲われないよ
Huh?
えっ?
why?
なんで?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Because it's getting closer.
近づくから
Huh?
えっ?
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
No.
ダメだよ
OF.
NG
OF?
NG?
Who said it well?
誰がうまいこと言えたの?
Nude G.
ヌードG
Nude G, right?
ヌードGでしょ?
But you feel safe here, right?
でも、ここだけさ、 安心してるんでしょ?
This is what's bothering me.
ここがらわきなんだよ
I don't feel safe.
安心してない
Shouldn't it be me?
俺ならいいんじゃないの?
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
Look.
ほら
Which is more embarrassing?
どっちが恥ずかしい?
Can you see it?
見られる?
Both.
どっちもだ
well,
じゃ、
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
じゃ んけんしよっか
Because I think it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいと思うから
See if you win this.
これ勝ったら見して
Look carefully.
ちゃんと見して
At first it was goo, rock, paper, scissors, hey.
最初はグー、じゃんけん、おい
Now it's Aiko.
これで、あいこでしょ
Won three times.
3回勝った
No, no.
ダメ、ダメ
But being embarrassed makes me want to be mean.
でも、恥ずかしいほうが、 意地悪したくなるんだよ
Look!
ほら!
ほ ら!
G: Well, I'm a pervert.
Gはさ、 俺、変態だけどさ
You're a pervert.
変態じゃん
When did you start growing up?
いつ頃から大きくなったんですか?
Around 5th grade.
小学5年生くらい
early.
早い
Is it just about this size?
このサイズぐらいまでやっとくらいなの?
Is that how much you branded it?
それぐらいにブランドつけたってこと?
They'll tell you, right?
教えてくれるんだね、ちゃんとね
Don't tell me.
内緒だぞ
Because it’s me?
俺だから?
It's no good, if you tell me it's that male student.
ダメだよ、その男子生と教えたら
Is it no good?
ダメか
Teacher, how many cups?
先生、何カップですか?
Like.
みたいな
It's G.
Gだぞ
No, I said.
ダメだよ、言ったら
I won't say it.
言わないよ
TRUE?
本当?
I won't say it.
言わない
That's what it is.
そういうことだね
We'll compete again.
また勝負するじゃん
Okay.
いいよ
From the beginning.
最初から
Cheating!
ずる!
Because it's a serious competition.
真面目勝負だから
There's no cheating.
ズ ルとかないよ
Those are the words of a precious thing.
貴重物の台詞だ
Well then, let's go.
じゃあ、いきますね
You can take care of it.
手当てていいから
Just a little skirt.
スカートだけちょっと
Ah, I saw it.
あ、見えた
cool.
かっこいい
What?
え、何?
Something like this will happen soon.
すぐでしょ、こういうこと
Because I'm filming it with a camera.
カメラで撮ってるからさ
It's always different though.
いつも違うけど
I lost, so it's no good.
負けたんだから、ダメだよ
But it's fine.
でも、していいよね
It's been a while.
久しぶりだった
I haven't fully accepted the pump yet.
まだパンプ完全に受け入れてないから
Just a little more.
もうちょっとだけ
Try sitting down.
座ってみて
Follow my instructions.
俺の指示に従って
Go to the side for a moment.
ちょっと横に行って
Raise your legs.
両足上げて
Open your legs.
足開いて
Oh, I don't like it.
え、嫌だ
Haven't you heard this far?
ここまで聞いてくれてないの?
Suddenly?
急に?
Open your legs.
足開いて
Should I open my legs or raise my arms like this?
足開くか、こうやって 腕を上げるか、
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
Yeah, like this.
そうそう、こうやって
where are you standing?
どこに立ってるの?
Forbidden.
禁断の
show me.
見せて
It's forbidden for future teachers.
次期教師の禁断なわけ
What do you think you'll do now?
今から何すると思う?
hand
手
Because it's open.
開 いてるから
I'm a pervert.
俺、変態だよ
Raise your legs too.
足も上げて
show me.
見せて
You can't see it with your legs spread apart.
足開いてて見えないでしょ
Eh, more?
え、もっと?
Spread your legs apart.
足開いて広げて
The old man also does this.
おっさんもこうやって
I don't like it.
嫌だ
sorry.
ごめん
You won't be embarrassed if you see it.
見たら恥ずかしなくなるよね
Look.
ごらん
You look good in that underwear too.
似合ってるね、その下着もね
If I don't open my legs, the smell will stop again.
足開かないと、またわけに匂いかがやむ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I also want to see the back of the pants.
パンツの後ろ側もよく見たい
What happens if you go out?
付き出すとどうなる?
Why does it smell?
なんで匂いかいなの?
Sorry for a moment.
ちょっとごめん
You can see people today too.
今日の人も見てかるな
Sorry.
ごめんね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしよね
Look.
ごらん
I won't say it.
言わないよ
face
顔 して
Ru.
る
It's true.
本当 だよ
Solid.
しっかり
Reflected.
映って
It looks very clear.
めっちゃしっかり映ってる
Did you see it this time? From here.
今回見たのよっか、ここから
You don't have to see it.
見なくていい
It looks really good.
めっちゃしっかり映ってるよ
Is that so?
そう か
It's reflected.
映ってる
That's sneaky.
ずるいって、それ
He licked my breath.
息を舐めたって
It's very dirty.
めっちゃ汚れてる
Don't ring.
鳴らさないで
You don't have to show it.
見せなくていい
Don't show it.
見せないで
Shall I go to sleep?
寝ていこうか
I'll go.
行くよ
arrival.
到着
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
That's where it's wet, can I look at it from here?
そこもさ、 濡れてるとこさ、 ここから見ていい?